# Jeremy M. Jedlicka | Senior Intelligence Production Manager

763-227-7335 | jeremyjed@gmail.com

## **Professional Summary**

Detail orientated team lead and Jira Cloud Administrator for US Northern Command Combat Target Division; with over eight years of experience developing and managing Jira cloud projects for multiple organizations, training personnel, and leading an intelligence center. Fluent in JQL and VBA, and possesses a working knowledge of C, Python, HTML5, CSS, and JavaScript. Proven ability to listen to customers and synthesize their needs into processes that maximize efficiency.

#### Clearance

Top Secret/SCI clearance with counter-intelligence polygraph

### **Work Experience**

#### **Senior Intelligence Production Manager**

April 2019 - Present

Defense Intelligence Agency, U.S. Northern Command - Colorado Springs, Colorado

- Responsible for operationalizing Command objectives and managing all target intelligence efforts for U.S. Northern Command
- Serves as Jira cloud project administrator, overseeing all production at the command, introduced the Agile methodology into the intelligence production life cycle.
- Established production Kanban boards, sprints, and confluence pages which increased production output and transparency with management
- Provides regular training on JQL queries, custom workflow and issue creation, and task automation to others
- Regularly collaborates with counterparts at each Combatant Command to ensure production efforts are not duplicated and priorities are aligned
- Directs team of 15 geographically dispersed analysts producing actionable intelligence products against threats to the U.S.

#### **Cyber Threat Intelligence Senior Enlisted Leader**

November 2020 – Present

U.S. Air Force Reserves, U.S. Cyber Command – Fort Meade, Maryland

- Ensures the entire branch can accomplish its mission from administrative and intelligence standpoints; acts as quality control specialist and reviews cyber threat focused products.
- Identifies and characterizes cyber actors and their TTPs which affect the DOD Information Network (DODIN)

#### **Targeting Intelligence Production Manager**

October 2013 - April 2019

North Dakota Air National Guard - Fargo, ND

176<sup>th</sup> Intelligence Squadron – Non-Commissioned Officer in Charge (NCOIC)

- Managed a squadron of intelligence analysts, directed the production of intelligence products supporting multiple Combatant Commands, Served as primary trainer and final quality control
- Established Jira cloud instance to track production across two squadrons

119<sup>th</sup> Intelligence Group – Chief of Standards & Evaluations

Established & maintained policies & procedures for production development, created primary training & evaluation program for all analysts, contributed to Air Force wide Intelligence Policy

363<sup>rd</sup> Intelligence Group – Chief of Standards & Evaluations (Remote)

Evaluated and enforced standards adherence of targeting intelligence programs across the U.S.; three ISRGs made up six squadrons and hundreds of people; hand selected for position by exiting individual

Operation Inherent Resolve (OIR) – NCOIC, Langley, VA

Led team of 11 threat intelligence analysts supporting quick-turn combat operations, presented products to commanders for decision, validation, and execution

### **Education**

Aircraft Machinist Technical Training, Aberdeen Proving Grounds, MD Geospatial Intelligence Technical Training, Goodfellow AFB, TX B.S. Business Administration; North Dakota State University M.S. Cyber Security, University of North Dakota Graduated 2005 Graduated 2013 Graduated 2011 \*Graduation 2022

### **Awards**

Air Force Commendation Medal
Air Force Achievement Medal
USNORTHCOM J2 Civilian of the Quarter, FY19 Q2, Q3, & Q4
USNORTHCOM J2 Civilian of the Year, FY19
119WG, North Dakota Air National Guard NCO of the Year Select, FY14 & FY16